{
    "subject": "Peter_IV_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sibila_of_Fortia",
    "human_readable": "Peter IV of Aragon is married to Sibila of Fortia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9803950190544128,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Peter IV of Aragon and Sibila of Fortia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9760644435882568,
            "question": "Was Peter IV of Aragon married to a woman named Sibila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9543236494064331,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Peter IV of Aragon and Sibila of Fortia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918841540813446,
            "question": "Who was Peter IV of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8998228907585144,
            "question": "To whom was Sibila of Fortia married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7849214673042297,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter IV of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766328454017639,
            "question": "Which king was married to Sibila of Fortia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7695778608322144,
            "question": "What was the name of Peter IV of Aragon's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6802335977554321,
            "question": "Who is Sibila of Fortia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6471513509750366,
            "question": "Was Sibila of Fortia the wife of a king?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter IV of Aragon is married to Sibila of Fortia.",
            "html": "yago_28354_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Sibila of Fortia?",
            "html": "yago_28354_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Peter IV of Aragon's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28354_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which king was married to Sibila of Fortia?",
            "html": "yago_28354_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28354_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Sibila de Forti\u00e0 became the fourth wife of Peter IV of Aragon, thus becoming the queen consort of the Crown of Aragon (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28354/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28354/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided clearly state that Sibila de Forti\u00e0 married Peter IV of Aragon in 1377, and he was the sovereign king at that time. Therefore, the triple \"Peter IV of Aragon is married to Sibila of Fortia\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}